{
    "subject": "resource/Shaw_University",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "resource/William_Gaston_Pearson",
    "human_readable": "Shaw University's name is William Gaston Pearson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9479347467422485,
            "question": "Is there a connection between William Gaston Pearson and Shaw University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8877204060554504,
            "question": "Who is William Gaston Pearson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773047685623169,
            "question": "What was Shaw University originally named?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5849331617355347,
            "question": "What type of institution is Shaw University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45796385407447815,
            "question": "What are some notable alumni of Shaw University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41344889998435974,
            "question": "Where is Shaw University located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3915278911590576,
            "question": "Are there any interesting facts about Shaw University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37219393253326416,
            "question": "When was Shaw University founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32902708649635315,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the history of Shaw University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2631593346595764,
            "question": "What academic programs does Shaw University offer?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shaw University's name is William Gaston Pearson.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5685_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the history of Shaw University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5685_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Shaw University founded?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5685_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any interesting facts about Shaw University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5685_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5685_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the history, location, and affiliations of Shaw University, but there is no mention of William Gaston Pearson being associated with naming or founding Shaw University. The documents related to William Gaston Pearson discuss his life and contributions in Durham, North Carolina, not his connection to Shaw University."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}